(Raj:)I'll be over here
basting my ass off.
(Raj:)Focus is key.
(Amy:)Did you guys know Penny
married Zack three years ago?
(Together:)-What?
-Wha...?
(Howard:)You ever play football?
(Mike:)A little in college.
(Sheldon:)-You?
-No.
(Howard:)But I did get tackled
in the hallway once.
(Howard:)The whole school cheered.
I found the, court papers
(Leonard:)that you and Zack
need to fill out.
(Leonard:)-I'll print them when we get home.
-Fine.
(Leonard:)And we can just put this
whole thing behind us.
(Penny:)Are you done?
(Together:)-What?
-Look, I get it, I screwed up.
Is this all we're going to talk
about the rest of the day?
(Leonard:)Why are you mad at me?
(Leonard:)You're the one that
did the stupid thing.
(Leonard:)-I'm just trying to fix it.
-(GROANS) I need some air.
Well... Penny.
Now, I don't know the
first thing about women,
(Sheldon:)but I would not follow her.
(Mike:)Listen to Stretch.